<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-04-28T16:57:46-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">California Theme</title><entry><title type="html">Here at Immanuel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome/2016/08/04/here-at-immanuel.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Here at Immanuel" /><published>2016-08-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-08-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/welcome/2016/08/04/here-at-immanuel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome/2016/08/04/here-at-immanuel.html">&lt;p&gt;Here at Immanuel Baptist Church it is our desire that this would be a place where people from all different walks of life can come and have their lives enriched by the power and grace that only God can provide. We are a group of people from all different backgrounds and life experiences and yet we are seeing God do some amazing things. We are a group of people who have taken our hurts, our habits, and hang-ups and laid them at the cross of Jesus and allowed Him to do something amazing with those things. Much like a mosaic you would find at a cathedral where a bunch of broken pieces of glass have been pieced together to make a masterpiece, so God is taking those parts of our lives and piecing them together to make something extraordinary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here at Immanuel Baptist Church we want to see God enrich lives through Christ. We do that through building genuine relationships with one another, through authentic worship, through compassionate evangelism in our community and then finally, through biblical preaching and teaching. The Gospels tell us that the Word of God is truth and it is the truth that makes us free. So if you and your family are looking for a place where your life can be enriched by the power and grace of God, we hope that you would come by and visit soon. If there is every anything we can do for you, please don’t hesitate to let us know. May the Lord bless you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pastor Castro</name></author><summary type="html">Here at Immanuel Baptist Church it is our desire that this would be a place where people from all different walks of life can come and have their lives enriched by the power and grace that only God can provide. We are a group of people from all different backgrounds and life experiences and yet we are seeing God do some amazing things. We are a group of people who have taken our hurts, our habits, and hang-ups and laid them at the cross of Jesus and allowed Him to do something amazing with those things. Much like a mosaic you would find at a cathedral where a bunch of broken pieces of glass have been pieced together to make a masterpiece, so God is taking those parts of our lives and piecing them together to make something extraordinary. Here at Immanuel Baptist Church we want to see God enrich lives through Christ. We do that through building genuine relationships with one another, through authentic worship, through compassionate evangelism in our community and then finally, through biblical preaching and teaching. The Gospels tell us that the Word of God is truth and it is the truth that makes us free. So if you and your family are looking for a place where your life can be enriched by the power and grace of God, we hope that you would come by and visit soon. If there is every anything we can do for you, please don’t hesitate to let us know. May the Lord bless you.</summary></entry></feed>